(Raj:)Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere. Don't move.
(Raj:)Just stay the beautiful unspoiled
American flower that you are.
What's wrong with you, dude?
That woman is all up on my jammy.
(Leonard:)Okay, I hate to break this to you
and whatever your jammy is...
...but I'm pretty sure she's a prostitute.
(Raj:)What?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Okay, let me put it this way.
(Leonard:)In your entire life, how many gorgeous
women have walked up to you at a bar...
...and asked if you wanted to party?
(Raj:)Maybe I can save her.
Maybe. But I'm guessing it'll cost you
about $500 an hour to try.
(Raj:)It was lovely meeting you.
Best of luck in your future endeavors.
(Leonard:)Whatever.
(Raj:)Oh, I miss her already.